我和哥哥们是有史以来最古老的吸血鬼
My brothers and I are the first vampires,
也就是...始祖家族
in all of history-- the originals.
三百年前 新奥尔良城是我们的家园
300 years ago, we called New Orleans home.
曾经有一段时间 我在这里很快乐
I was happy here...for a time.
本视频由 时光机字幕组 制作发布
字幕仅限学习  严禁用于任何商业行为
现在我重新回来 却发现一个奇迹
Now we've returned, only to find a miracle...
Niklaus 这个女孩怀着你的孩子
Niklaus, the girl is carrying your child.
翻译:  李铭烟  Harriet  丸子  小咪  小梅  小雪  Yuffy
因为这个 我们有了新的责任
And with it, a new responsibility...
我会永远保护你
I will always protect you.
我向你保证
You have my word on that.
校对:  范遥  纪晓芙
但我们家族有很多敌人
But our family has many enemies.
Klaus毁了我生命中一切美好的东西
Klaus destroyed everything good in my life.
所以我要拿走他最想要的
So I'm gonna take away the thing he wants most.
这些威胁本应该让我们团结起来
These threats should have united us.
时间轴:  Jer-Knigんt
然而Klaus却将我们分离
Instead, Klaus has driven us apart.
在你对Elijah做出那种事之后
Why should I help you
我为什么还要帮你？
after what you did to Elijah?
监制:  杨逍
因为你是我的家人
You're my family.
Klaus永远不会停止对你的控制
Klaus will never stop trying to control you.
你想要的是什么？
What do you want?
一千年以来我哥哥希望我忠于他
My brother expects my loyalty,
一如既往的 但现在 也许
as he has for 1,000 years, but now, perhaps,
是时候做出另一个选择了
it's time to make another choice.
我根本就不应该回到这里
I should never have come back here.
这是我坠入爱河的城市
This is the town where I fell in love
也是我们对爱失望的城市
and where love failed us.
我猜你知道我在说谁
I assume you know who I'm talking about.
你应该知道 我和Marcel
You should know, Marcel and I
现在关系不是很好
aren't on the best of terms right now.
但你是个称职的神父 不是吗
But you are an active priest, are you not,
准备好听我的忏悔了吗？
ready and able to hear my confession?
通常情况下 “愿意”
Usually, the word "Willing"
会出现在这个句子里
falls somewhere in that sentence.
你连天主教徒都不是吧？
Are you even Catholic?
我已经活了1000年了
I've been on this earth for 1,000 years.
我不能确切地说我信仰上帝什么的
I can't say for certain that I believe in anything like a god,
但我需要得到宽恕
but I need absolution
不管是谁的 谁都可以
from someone, anyone.
所以你愿不愿意听我的忏悔呢？
So will you hear my confession or not?
神父 请原谅我的罪行
Bless me, father, for I have sinned.
我是一个骗子 一个叛徒
I am a liar, a betrayer.
我密谋策反我的血亲
I have conspired against my own blood,
我甚至怀疑上帝也不能拯救我
and I doubt even your god could save me.
24小时前
你今天和我们的好朋友Marcel聊天了吗？
Have you spoken to our good friend Marcel today?
没有 我应该说些什么吗？
No. Should I have?
他最近安静得有些奇怪
Well, he's been mysteriously silent,
有意无意地躲着我
avoiding me, some might say.
我想 他在你们卿卿我我的时候
I thought, perhaps, he may have whispered
可能对你
reasons into your ear
说过什么悄悄话
along with all of those sweet nothings.
如果我看到他了 一定会问问
If I see him, I'll be sure to ask
他是否还生你的气
if he's still sore at you.
让我给你的眼神做个解释吧
Let me give a voice to that look in your eyes.
我儒雅高尚的哥哥被混蛋的哥哥咬伤了
My saintly, noble brother lies writhing
正痛苦地躺在河口的小屋
in agony in the bayou,
垂死挣扎
victim of my bastard brother's bite
虽然只要一两滴他的血
when just one or two drops
就能缓解他的疼痛
of his blood would ease his pain.
恰恰相反 Nik
One the contrary, Nik.
我很享受边吃早餐
I am simply enjoying my brekkie
边等着Elijah健康回来
waiting for Elijah's healthy return.
得了吧 Rebekah
Oh, come on, Rebekah.
你整个早上都恶狠狠地盯着我
You've been giving me the devil's eye all morning.
你就承认吧
Out with it.
也许我只是在担心 万一我评价了
Perhaps I'm concerned that if I voice my opinion
你对Elijah的所作所为
about what you did to Elijah, I will end up
弄不好也会挨你咬一口
on the wrong side of your toxic hybrid teeth.
胡说八道 我永远不会咬你
Poppycock. I would never bite you.
Elijah对我做了过分的谴责
Elijah made some very offensive accusations
居然说我对自己的孩子居心叵测
about my intentions towards my child.
他活该难受这么一两天
He deserves a day or two of discomfort.
而且 你知道我更喜欢
Besides, you know my preferred method
用什么来惩罚你的轻率之举
of punishment for your indiscretions
匕首
is the dagger.
你从根本上就有问题
There's something fundamentally wrong with you.
来 喝了它
Here. Drink this.
请原谅我
Forgive me, please.
没关系
It's ok.
提醒我 一等你恢复过来
Remind me to annihilate your brother
就去灭了你的弟弟
once you're healthy.
好 记得提醒我告诉你
Yes. Remind me to remind you
得先排队挂个号
to get in line.
我们要留在这个沼泽地
Doesn't help that we decided to shack up
也无济于事
in the middle of a swamp, either.
-你还好吗？  -我很好
-Are you ok?  -I'm fine.
请继续读书吧
Please just return to your reading.
我浏览了整本书
Well, I went through the whole thing.
这只是本普通的圣经
It's just a regular bible
里面记录了一个族谱而已
with an entry in the family tree
那个名字也不一定是我
that may or may not be me,
但你知道我还是一直
but you know I've been a little busy
都在担心你
worrying about you.
Hayley 别这样
Hayley, please.
这种高烧会让我情绪很不稳定
This fever will make me unstable.
一旦开始出现幻觉
Now, once these hallucinations begin,
我会看到幻象
I'll start to see things.
然后胡言乱语
I will start to say things.
你必须让我一个人待在这里
You must leave me here.
我不会在这种情况把你留下的
I'm not leaving you like this.
我来了 我们开始吧
All right. I'm here. Let's do this.
我会长话短说
I'll keep this simple.
这孩子是你最爱的Klaus的一个宿敌
This kids is an old enemy of your favorite person Klaus.
现在 他有话要说
Now, he's got plenty to say
关于那个叛逆不忠的贱人
about what that traitorous
都瞒着我干了些什么
son of a bitch has been up to behind my back.
现在 胆小的人
Now, for those of you faint of heart,
门在那边 因为只要留下
there's the door because those who stick around,
就要参加战斗
you're signing up for battle.
众所周知 Klaus不会一直都是混血的状态
You all know Klaus wasn't always the hybrid.
当他打破他狼人的休眠诅咒时
When he broke the curse that kept his werewolf side dormant,
在某个方面
somewhere in all that,
就抑制了他的吸血鬼的一面
certain parts were now able to trump his vampire side,
比如能传递狼人的基因
like the ability to pass on the werewolf gene.
这就要说起他一直背着你们带着的那个狼女
That's where the werewolf girl he's been hiding from you all comes in.
她来到我住的小镇 装作是我的朋友
She rolled through my town, pretended to be my friend,
结果却和他勾搭在了一起
and ended up hooking up with him.
现在 她怀了他的孩子
Now she's pregnant with his kid.
怎么可能？
What the hell is this?
听着就好
Just listen.
当Klaus变成混血后
When Klaus became the hybrid,
他找到了方法让纯种狼人
he figured out a way to turn full-bred werewolves
变成像他一样的混血
into creatures like him.
我就是他们之中的一个
You're looking at one of them.
我们的优势是 拥有吸血鬼的所有能力
On the plus side, we had all the perks of being vampires.
还更强壮 更敏捷
We were stronger, faster,
我们咬人时分泌出的毒素依然可以杀死吸血鬼
and the toxins in our bites could still kill a vampire,
但劣势是 我们都效忠于他
but on the downside, we were loyal to him,
是非主动的忠诚
like, supernaturally loyal.
哦 这就是你在这里泄露他秘密的原因？
Right, and that's why you're here spilling all his secrets?
不 这就是重点 Diego
No. That's the point, Diego.
他找到了一个方法恢复自由
He figured out a way to break free of it.
我后来也帮助其他人这样
And I helped the rest of them, too.
但因为他们背叛了Klaus 他把他们都杀掉了
Then Klaus killed them for their betrayal.
因为Klaus容不下背叛
Because that is what Klaus does.
别介意
Don't mind me.
我只是被这故事吸引了
I'm fascinated by this story.
-嗨 Tyler  -Rebekah
-Hello, Tyler.  -Rebekah.
好久不见
Long time no see.
Tyler想跟你们说的是
What Tyler is about to tell you
我哥哥可以利用他孩子的血
is that my brother can use his baby's blood
来让更多的混血认祖归宗
to sire more hybrids.
而且吸血鬼根本没有胜算
What you will all figure out is that vampires don't stand a chance.
所以 Tyler 我猜你接下来正打算团结这些人
So, Tyler, I assume you were trying to rally this lot
确保这个孩子不会出生
into making sure the baby isn't born.
没错
Yeah.
你要不喜欢 可以站在你哥哥那边
You don't like it, go ahead and take your brother's side,
但是你知道 我是对的
but you know I'm right.
我相信你误解了这位女士的本意
I believe you've mistaken the lady's intentions.
那现在是什么情况？
All right. What's going on?
你是对的 Tyler
You're absolutely right, Tyler.
我哥哥是一个极品混蛋
My brother is a crap enough individual as it is.
不能再让他制造一群更优越的物种群
The last thing he needs is to sire a superior species.
来吧 你帮我说两句好话
Go on. You can tell them.
她不是来踢馆的
She's not here to fight us.
她是来帮我们的
She's here to help us.
没错 但是首先...
That's right, but first--
唔 要伤害婴儿的话题就说到这吧
whew, that is enough talk about harming that baby.
Klaus才是我们要制止的人
Klaus is the one we're putting a stop to.
他们都抛弃了我
They have all forsaken me.
我的兄弟姐妹和我父母一样
My siblings are as deceitful and diseased
虚伪而又病态
as my parents ever were,
指责我为了一己之私利用自己的血脉
accusing me of using my baby for my own gain,
宁愿相信别人也不相信自己的血亲
trusting others before their own blood.
哦 给我用个笔记本你能死吗？
Ohh, would a laptop kill you?
那台打印机给海明威用都绰绰有余了
That typewriter was good enough for Hemmingway.
你们的确有相似之处...
Can see the resemblance--
酗酒和胡乱施暴
Booze and random acts of violence.
Elijah和Rebekah的恶毒谎言
Elijah and Rebekah have cut to the quick
深深地刺痛了我
with their vicious lies about me
我所做的一切都是为了赢得这场战斗
when all I've done is tried to win
为了从Marcel手里接过控制权
this battle of wills over Marcel's control
重新要回我们的家
of the quarter in order to reclaim our home.
请继续打
Type, please.
重点是什么？
What's the point?
你只是不断地在重复着相同事情
You just repeat the same thing over and over again.
Rebekah要背叛你 Elijah要扳倒你
Rebekah is out to get you. Elijah is out to get you.
有没有人不想置你于死地呢？
Is there anyone who isn't plotting your downfall?
我怀疑你只信赖自己的影子
I doubt you trust your own reflection.
如果匕首没有消失
If the daggers weren't missing,
我肯定会在他俩心口上一人插一把
I would put one in each of their hearts,
让他们消停几个世纪 我也好耳根清净
rid myself of the burden of my siblings for a couple of centuries.
看看你自己
Look at you,
一次又一次地进入了 相同的破坏性周期
repeating the same destructive cycles over and over again.
你亲手造就了你的不幸
You are the architect of your own unhappiness.
我不记得我是来问你意见的
I don't remember asking for your advice.
哦真的吗？
Oh, really?
新奥尔良里有这么多人
So of all the people in New Orleans,
你偏选了一个有心理学硕士学位的人
you choose someone with a master's in psychology
去记录你的人生传记
to record your life story.
你都一千多岁了
You're over 1,000 years old.
肯定知道怎么打字啊
Pretty damn sure you know how to type.
真相是 你用意念操控我来这里
The truth is, you compel me to come here
因为没人可以倾诉
because you have no one else to talk to,
而你想要被人理解
and you want to be understood.
然后你再控制我 让我一离开你
Then you compel me to forget everything
就忘记所有事情
as soon as I leave your presence
因为你太害怕 没法信任别人
because you're too scared to trust.
我什么都不怕
I am scared of nothing.
这是什么？
What is this?
是个古老的神秘图绘 我要用它摧毁你
It's an ancient, mystical plot I’m using to destroy you.
放轻松 这是个纹身设计
Relax. It's a tattoo design.
你用自己的时间画画吧
Draw on your own time.
这就是我自己的时间 是你强占了
This is my time. You steal it from me.
你打算把他放在哪儿？
Where do you want him?
把他放在一边就好
Well, just put him anywhere handy
直到处理掉Klaus
until Klaus is taken care of.
我们要把Klaus放在哪儿？
Where are we gonna put Klaus?
他得离其他人远些
He needs to be away from all the others.
我们可不想让他再惹出什么事情
We don't want him fomenting descent.
你懂得 他很会说花言巧语
You know he has a knack with words.
很有可能凭嘴皮子就能逃出去
He could talk his way out of hell.
是啊 所以我在后面给他选了个地方
Yeah. I got a spot picked out for him in the back.
在未来的五十二年里他唯一可以对话的
Only person he's gonna be talking to
就是他自己
for the next 52 years is himself.
五十二年？
52?
因为他在十九世纪的时候用匕首封印了你五十二年
One for each year that he kept you daggered in the 1800s.
你指你任由他捅我的那次
You mean, you let him keep me daggered.
Klaus在这里的每一年 我都会向你道歉的
And I'll spend every year Klaus is in here apologizing to you for it.
那我得花足够的时间
Well, I'll settle for long enough
去体验一下这小小的快乐了
to experience just a little bit of happiness
还得保证我的侄女不会变成
and ensure that my niece isn't turned
一个繁殖混血的机器
into a hybrid breeding machine.
要把他困在这里很难
It's gonna be tough to keep him in here.
你那个小女巫
That little witch of yours
会增加我们成功的可能性的
would put the odds in our favor.
我不能冒这个险
I can't risk it.
最近她的魔法越来越失控
She's got less and less control over her magic lately.
我甚至都不能让她离开教堂阁楼
I can't even get her out of the church attic,
更不能指望依赖她去对付Klaus
much less rely on her to go to battle against Klaus.
那我们就需要你最厉害的战士了
Then we'll need your very best warriors.
Klaus强大又狡猾
Klaus is strong and crafty,
背叛会让他更加怒不可遏
and betrayal makes him particularly nasty.
我们对Klaus所做的
What we're doing is nothing Klaus
都是他对你和你哥哥做过的
hasn't done to both you and your brother
还做了很多次
a dozen times over.
你现在不会是在动摇吧？
You're not getting second thoughts now, are you?
不 不是动摇
No. These aren't second thoughts.
只是很后悔
They're feelings of regret.
我几百年前就应该把他埋了的
I should've buried him a hundred years ago.
这一百年的时间我们本来可以一直在一起的
It's a hundred years we could've been together.
没事了 没事了
It's ok. It's ok.
哦 Celeste
Oh, Celeste.
Hayley 对不起
Hayley, I'm sorry.
我把你当成别人了
I thought you were someone else.
-Celeste？ -是的
- Celeste? - Yes.
不管她是谁 真的好性感
Whoever she was, she was smoking hot.
怎么...
How--
我让你进入我的思想了？
Did I let you enter my thoughts?
我不舒服 该走了
I'm not well. I should go.
-这真是... -没事的
- This is-- - This is fine.
Elijah 你病了 我在照顾你
Elijah, you're sick. I'm taking care of you.
有人监视我们
We're being watched.
哦 天啊 我没办法习惯
Oh, man, I'll never get used to that.
为什么我总觉得你学过戏剧呢？
Why do I get the feeling you studied theater?
这整个世界就是一个舞台 小Joshua
All the world's a stage, young Joshua,
巧的是我在你一生中
and it just so happens I have
都是个举足轻重的角色
the role of a lifetime for you.
有什么消息么 Josh？
What do you got, Josh?
我有什么消息？！
What do I got?
Klaus想让我从你这儿偷一把什么匕首
Klaus wants me to steal some dagger from you.
这是个测试 好吗？
It's a test, ok?
他知道我在帮你们做事了 我确定一定以及肯定
He knows I'm working for you. I'm sure of it.
那混蛋又想封印我们了
That bastard wants to dagger us again.
他活该遭报应
He deserves everything he's gonna get.
放松
Relax.
如果他知道了 这会儿你早就被撕成两半了
If he knew, he would've ripped out your spine through your nose by now.
哦 真棒
Oh, great.
现在我感到彻底轻松了
Now I feel totally at ease.
那我该怎么做？
What am I supposed to do?
告诉他到处都翻了个底朝天
You tell him you searched high and low
但就是没找到匕首
but you couldn't find the dagger.
哦 天爷 我死定了
Oh, god, I'm so dead.
然后你告诉他说 你看到过我随身带着它
Then you tell him you saw I had it on me,
如果他想要 就得亲自来取
that if he wants it, he'll have to come and get it,
这可不容易 因为我很多疑
which won't be easy because I'm paranoid
而且还增强了我队伍的力量
and I beefed up my posse.
好吧 我不是在怀疑你身为
All right. So, not doubting
疯狂吸血鬼能毁灭一切的本事
your mad vampire skills of destruction or anything,
但Marcel已经提高了警惕
but Marcel is on red alert,
组了一支军队保护他
surrounded by, like, an army.
你只是孤军奋战 除非..
You're totally boned unless--
除非什么？
Unless what?
我无意中听到他和Diego的争吵
I overheard him arguing with Diego.
很显然
Apparently,
他今晚会清理场地 赴个约什么的
he's clearing out the compound tonight for a date or something.
总之Marcel会在那儿
That's where Marcel will be.
待我统治新奥尔良时
When I run New Orleans,
我为你准备一枚永恒的日光戒的 Joshua
there will be a permanent daylight ring in it for you, Joshua,
作为你效忠真正的王者的赏赐
for services rendered unto your true king.
好极了
Cool.
但如果你胆敢背叛我
But if you ever betray me,
我保证你无尽的生命将活在极端的痛苦中
I will make sure you spend the rest of your eternal life
最后只求一死
in exquisite agony wishing for a merciful death.
永别了 Klaus[西语]
Adios, Klaus.
你想要什么？
What do you want?
这是Poi tin
It's Poi tín.
它能让人起死回生
It'd raise the dead,
杀了他们 再把他们复活
kill them, and raise them again.
我想谈谈你的侄女Camille
I'd like to talk to you about your niece Camille.
我知道你根据她记忆力的空隙
I'm sure you suspect this already
就会怀疑
by the gaps in her memory.
是我用意念控制了她
I compeled her.
起初是因为 她是个有用的间谍
At first, it was because she was a useful spy
但现在是为了保护她
but now for her own protection.
我一直觉得有个吸血鬼在扰乱她的心智
I assumed a vampire was messing with her mind,
尽管我没预料到你会供认不讳
though I never anticipated a confession.
但她不会这么轻易放下心结的
She won't leave things be.
她胞弟在教堂里大开杀戒
Her mind churns with the permutations
这一幕
of what happened in this church
在她的脑海里不断上演
when her twin when on his slaughter spree.
现在 如果她知道了这些事情的真相
Now, if she finds out what really happened,
知道了关于吸血鬼和女巫的魔法的事情
that the vampires and witch hexes were involved,
那她会深究下去 直到发现真相
she will dig and dig and dig until she digs too deep
为此惹来杀身之祸
and gets herself killed.
新奥尔良会成为她的葬身之地的
New Orleans will be the death of her.
她要离开
She needs to leave,
虽然有点讽刺的意思
and, as ironic as it may seem,
但我认为这应该是她自己的选择
I believe it should be her choice.
对 和一个会控制意念的吸血鬼谈论
Yes. It is ironic discussing free will
自由意志什么的确很讽刺
with a mind-controlling vampire.
她是个聪明的女人
She's a clever girl.
今早她刚教训了我一顿
She gave me a piece of her mind earlier today.
如果是别人我早就杀掉了
I would've killed others for less.
我在乎她的安危
I care about her survival.
我嗅到了战争的气息
I smell war in the air,
而每一场战争
and with every war,
都有无辜的牺牲者 如果他们及时离开
there is the innocent victim who could have been spared
原本是可以保住性命的
if they had just walked away.
请一定说服她离开新奥尔良
Please convince her to walk away from New Orleans,
不然我必须用意念控制她走
or I'll be forced to compel her to go.
这位绅士 能过来帮我吗
Assistance, please, good sir.
不 我更愿意站在这个角度欣赏
No. I'm much happier taking in such a wondrous view.
如此令人沉醉
It's perfection.
你的兄弟又不安分了
Your brother is again up to no good.
他挑衅贵族们跟他决斗
He's challenging the gentry to duels
好像他们能有公平决斗的机会似的
as though they have any chance of a fair fight.
我真厌倦了放弃自己美好的时光
I do grow weary of sacrificing my joy
来给我的弟弟收拾烂摊子了
to temper my brother's mischief.
我敢肯定你可以施个魔法
Surely, you can cast a spell,
让他老实一点吧
put him in his place.
那恐怕得有100个女巫同时施魔法才能办到了
It will take 100 witches to put him in his place.
而且 他从来只会听你的话
Besides, he only ever listens to you.
是
Yes.
他真的要学会点规矩了
He certainly needs a little discipline.
也许打屁股是个好办法
Perhaps a spanking of some kind is in order.
我想我需要练习几次 来
I think I shall need some rehearsal. Come.
Hayley 这场高烧...
Hayley, please. This fever.
那些痛苦的回忆如洪水般在我脑中翻滚
My mind is flooded with these tortuous memories.
你应该离开
You have to leave.
你这人怎么这样？
What is your deal?
你不希望有人照顾你吗？
You don't like people taking care of you?
关心别人没好下场
There are consequences for those that care.
我不会让你承受这些的
I will not have you pay that price.
你只是在做中世纪的春梦吧
So you're having weird retro sex dreams.
别想了 我会留下的
Get over it. I'm staying.
我们的客人怎么样了？
So what about our visitor?
她想要什么？
What does she want?
我猜她可能就是
I'm guessing she's the one that
昨晚把这本神秘的圣经放在门外的人
left the mystery bible on the doorstep last night.
如果她那时候能多留一会
Would be nice if she'd stick around
告诉我其中的缘由该多好
long enough to tell me why.
Hayley 你来这里是为了搜寻一些你家族的消息
Hayley, you came here to gather information about your family,
而不是照顾发烧吸血鬼的保姆
not to play nursemaid to a vampire with a temperature.
去吧 找到她 把你能问到的都问出来
Please...find her. Learn what you can.
不 我要留下来
No. I'm staying.
Klaus
Klaus.
你一直不接我的电话
You've been avoiding my calls.
我最近火气很大
A little pissed off lately.
待会我会为我的所作所为致以歉意
Apologies for my behavior can come later.
只是你身上有我的东西 我想把它拿回来
You have something of mine. I want it back.
抱歉 我不能这么做
Sorry, but I can't do that.
这是什么意思？
What is this?
为你的所作所为道歉？
Apologies for your behavior?
你从不会道歉的Nik 你只是装一下
You don't apologize, Nik. You just act.
我受够了 我们受够了
I've had enough. We have had enough.
瞧瞧你自己 终于拥有了
Well, look at you, finally in possession
唯一能扳倒你的东西
of the one thing that can take you down.
-感觉如何？ -好极了
- How does it feel? - Great.
原来如此
So this is it.
恶魔Klaus已经越线太多了
The evil bastard Klaus has gone too far,
所以必须受到惩罚
must be punished.
而且 还是由他的亲妹妹施行
And by his own sibling, nonetheless.
美妙如圣经
How positively biblical.
至于你 Marcel
And you, Marcel,
这就是你所谓的生死之战？
is this your idea of a hit?
我教你的可比这样微不足道的围捕强得多
I taught you better than this paltry excuse for a takedown.
你以为凭这些 就能征服我？
You think you can subdue me with this?
不 但我觉得这样就可以
No, but I think I can with this.
Celeste...
原谅我
Forgive me.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
准备决斗[法语]
A l'outrance.
八 七 六 五[法语]
Huit, sept, six, cinq,
四 三 二 ...[法语]
Quatre, trois, deux--
就这水平？
Is that it?
这就是新奥尔良最强的枪手？
Is this the best New Orleans has to offer?
弟弟 拜托 这太荒唐了
Brother, please. This is high folly.
过去的几周里你已经屠杀了那么多人
Is it not enough that you have slaughtered
难道还不够么？
dozens in just these past several weeks?
这个嘛...
Well--
城里堆满尸体的流言
Word of a city littered with bodies
会流传出去的
will surely travel the oceans.
你想把父亲引来吗？
Do you want to bring our father upon us?
放轻松 哥哥
Relax, brother.
我已经放出消息说这些尸体
I've sent rumor that the bodies are a result
是女巫们为了寻找血祭的牺牲品而造成的
of the witches seeking blood sacrifice for their rituals.
你干了什么？
You did what?
你忘了Celeste也是
Have you forgotten Celeste is one of those
你诬蔑的那些女巫中的一员么？
that you so recklessly pointed your finger at?
谁是Celeste？
Who's Celeste?
哦 我想起来了 就是那个你成天围着转的女巫
Oh, yes, the witch you've been knocking around with.
别担心
Well, fear not.
妓女就像法语区的老鼠
Harlots are like rats in the quarter.
你随便迈一步就能被一只绊倒
You trip over one every step you take.
你在乎她  这可真是不幸啊
You care about her. Well, that is unfortunate.
我听说这会儿他们正在围捕镇上的女巫
I hear they're rounding up the town's witches as we speak.
Elijah？啊！
Elijah? Oh!
Niklaus 你这个混蛋 我要杀了你
Niklaus, I'll kill you, you bastard.
Elijah？啊！
Elijah? Aah!
很高兴认识你
Hello to you, too.
咱结束这场哑谜游戏吧 怎么样？
Let's end this charade, shall we?
新奥尔良的吸血鬼们
Vampires of New Orleans,
一定要给我记得 我是个始祖 是个混血儿
do recall that I am an original, a hybrid.
我拥有不死之身
I cannot be killed.
永生是一段十分漫长的时光
Eternity is an awfully long time.
你们觉得Marcel还能掌权多久？
How long to you think Marcel will stay in power?
假如你们中的一个人帮我离开
What if one of you lot were to release me,
并知道这将得到我永生的感恩 会怎么样？
knowing I would be eternally in your debt?
哦 我同情那些敢与我对抗的人
Oh, I would pity those of you who dared to cross me.
我向你们保证
I can assure you,
你们一定会死得无比壮观的
your ends would be spectacular.
这是我从一个老朋友那里
To borrow a trick
学来的一个小把戏…
from an old friend...
谁能捡起这枚硬币
Whoever picks up this coin
谁就能活下来
gets to live.
现在 你们这些壮烈的杂种们
Now, which of you magnificent bastards
谁想跟我一伙呢？
wants to join me?
想要那枚硬币的人
Anyone wants that coin,
向Klaus宣誓效忠吧
pledge allegiance to Klaus,
现在就去
Take it now.
去吧 你们有选择权
Go ahead. The choice is yours.
拿下他
Take him.
Marcel！放马过来决一死战吧！
Marcel! Come and finish this!
不
No.
-捡起硬币 -什么？
- Take the coin. - What?
除非所有人都死了 不然他不会停止的
He won't stop until everyone is dead,
他也会杀了你的
and he will kill you, too.
让这一切结束吧 捡起那枚硬币
End this. Pick up the coin.
够了！
Enough!
瞧瞧
Well, well, well.
伟大的Marcel
The great Marcel,
自称为新奥尔良国王之人
self-proclaimed king of New Orleans,
正跪在我的面前
bowing before me.
给你
There.
我向您宣誓我的忠诚
I hereby pledge my allegiance to you.
您现在拥有我王国的钥匙了
You have the keys to my kingdom.
它是您的了
It's yours.
我正要回家
I was on my way home,
看见你躲在这里
saw you duck in here,
我就知道你会在这儿
knew exactly where you'd be.
这些恶作剧又来了
This is getting old.
这周第二次了
It's the second time this week.
是第三次
Third,
我前天才把这里擦干净
but I cleaned it off the day before yesterday.
一点用都没有 他们还会这么做的
It's pointless. They'll just do it again.
大家需要时间来治愈
Folks need time to heal.
Sean杀了无辜的人
Sean killed innocent people.
没有人能这么快摆脱心理阴影
No one is getting over that any time soon.
我觉得
I think--
我想我要像他一样发疯了
I think I'm losing it like he did.
我在口袋里找到了这个
I found this in my pocket.
这上面的线条
The lines,
是我和Sean小的时候
it's a secret code Sean and I
经常用的秘密代码
used to use when we were kids.
我不记得我画过这个了
I have no memory of drawing it.
我不知道哪里出了问题 但总觉得不对劲
Something is not right. I just can't figure it out.
过来 没事的
Come here. Oh...
也许你应该离开镇里一阵子了
Maybe you should leave town for a while...
给自己一点时间放松
Give your head some space.
我认识你的院长
I know your dean.
你可以晚一点交论文
You could put your thesis on hold.
不行
I can't.
这一定意味着什么
This means something.
只是我还不知道而已
I just don't know what.
不是所有的东西都有什么寓意的
Not everything has meaning.
有时你要学会放下
Sometimes you just have to let go.
你应该离开新奥尔良
You should leave New Orleans.
并不是所有的人都适合在这生活
This town isn't for everybody.
离开吧
Please.
我敢肯定你有很多的疑问
I'm sure you got questions.
也就一千多个吧
Only a thousand of them,
比如你是谁
Like who are you,
为什么跟踪我
why are you following me,
其他人都去了那里
where the hell is everyone,
还有 如果书中记载的人
and if the people in this book
真的是我的家人 他们发生了什么？
really are my family, what happened to them?
我叫Eve
I'm Eve.
我跟踪你是因为
I'm following you because you brought
你把一个始祖吸血鬼带到了狼人的领地
an original to werewolf country,
而正是因为这个原因
which is pretty much the same reason
其他人都逃走了
why everybody else skedaddled,
如果你想知道
and if you want to know what happened
族谱上的人都发生了什么事
to the people in that family tree,
简而言之
summing it up nice and quick,
都拜赐于Marcel
Marcel happened.
他做了什么？
What did he do?
他杀死了大部分狼人
He killed most of them.
后来 为了对付那些
Later, the descendents of the ones
幸存者的后代 他迫使一位女巫
who dodged death, he strong-armed a witch
对他们下了咒
into putting a curse on them.
什么样的咒语？
What kind of curse?
完全颠覆了自然规律 从内部
Swap nature around, inside out,
使他们的自然状态变成狼形
made it so their natural state was wolves.
只能在满月时才能变回人身
they only turn back human on the full moon.
我们因为身上有那枚标记而遭到猎杀
We get hunted by the marks we carry,
就是那枚月牙形的胎记
that crescent moon birthmark.
所以我把自己的那个毁掉了
That's why I got rid of mine.
我不想被发现
I didn't want to get found out.
晚上好啊
Good evening.
我想你可能
Think I might have
有什么东西落在我这里了
something which belongs to you.
Elijah 我来处理这个 你还好吗？
Elijah, I've got this. Are you ok?
伤口已经愈合 体温也降下来了
The wound had healed, the fever has broken,
但是奇怪的是
but for some strange reason,
我的背部却依旧有种锐痛挥之不去
I have this sharpened lingering sensation in my back.
我必须带他回去了 但是我会回来的 好吗？
I have to get him home, but I'll be back, ok?
我需要知道更多信息
I need to know more.
遮好你的印记
Keep that mark covered up.
发生什么事了？
What happened?
我刚只是见到了我的家人
I just met part of my family.
看看你做的好事
Looking at what you've wrought?
听着 如果你想杀了我
Look. If you're gonna kill me,
那就动手吧
let's get this over with.
我为什么要杀你？
Why would I kill you?
你捡起了银币
You picked up the coin.
Marcel 每一场战斗都有交战规则
There are rules of engagement in battle, Marcel.
没有规矩 不成方圆
Without them, you'd have anarchy.
但是 我更想谈谈
I would, however, like to talk
战利品
about accommodations,
比如说 你的领地
your living quarters, for example.
我相信它们曾经是属于我的
I believe they used to be mine.
你想要这一切？ 可以 都是你的了
You want all this? Fine. It's yours.
你可以把我驱逐到街上做小弟 都没关系
You can put me back on the street for all I care,
但是有件事我要和你说清楚
but let's make one thing clear.
你永远都得不到的是这个...
You'll never have this--
忠诚
loyalty.
你买不到  得不到
You can't buy it. You can't own it.
更强求不来
You can't force it.
它仅仅源于那些信任你的人
It comes only out of love and respect
对你的爱和尊重
for the people who believe in you.
你教过我很多东西 Niklaus Mikaelson
You taught me many things, Niklaus Mikaelson,
但这一个 是我自己学到的
but this I learned myself,
也是你永远都不会领悟到的
and it is something that you will never know.
尽情享受你的王国吧
Enjoy your kingdom.
谢谢你载我回来
So thanks for the ride.
真是一次尴尬的冒险旅程啊 不是吗？
Quite the awkward, little adventure, wouldn't you say?
抱歉我曾要伤害你
I'm sorry I tried to hurt you.
我从未想那么做
I would never want that.
Elij...
Elij--
告诉我Celeste发生了什么事
Tell me what happened to Celeste.
那不重要
That's not important.
那很重要
It is important.
你有着一千年的记忆
1,000 years of memories,
但是当你发烧的时候却偏偏想到她？
and that's what breaks through your fever brain?
我想知道 带我看吧
I want to know. Show me.
对于女巫来说那是一个残忍而血腥的时代
It was a cruel and bloody time to be a witch.
承蒙我那伟大的弟弟的好意
Courtesy of my wonderful brother.
Klaus杀了她？
She died because of Klaus?
她是因我而死
She died because of me,
因为我太在乎她
because I cared too deeply for her.
我任由弟弟在我的眼皮底下放纵
I had allowed my brother to slip through my grasp.
Celeste占据我所有思绪的时候 我就失去了对他的控制
I'd loosened the reins while Celeste consumed my every moment.
我以自己的幸福为名义放纵了他
I'd abandoned him in the name of my own happiness.
而Celeste却为此付出代价
Celeste paid the price.
我不明白 为什么我们要回来？
I don't get it. Why are we here?
为什么明明知道你的家庭已经破碎
Why are you trying to put together your family
你还是想要将它拼凑在一起？
when it's so clear that one part of it is broken?
对我来说 "破碎"这一词的特别意义就在于
To me, the very definition of the word
它还是可以修复的
"Broken" suggests that something can be fixed.
我有无尽的时间可以去完成
I have all eternity to accomplish
一个唯一的任务 那就是我弟弟的救赎
one single task-- my brother's salvation.
而如果我屈服了 那么你告诉我
If I surrender this, then, tell me,
我对我的家人 对我自己
what value would I be to my family, to myself, to--
对你的孩子 还有什么价值？
to your child?
求你了 不要这样  Hayley
Please, no, Hayley.
不要再重蹈覆辙了
You've seen what happens.
Elijah也回来了 现在只有一把匕首
Elijah is home. There's only one dagger.
今天你要惩罚我们两个中的谁？
Which one of us will you be punishing today?
我想到了一个游戏
I contemplated a game
猜兵猜将
of eeny meeny miny moe.
你背叛了我 我的亲妹妹
You betrayed me, my own sister.
Niklaus 你敢
Niklaus, don't you dare.
也许会从你下手 哥哥
Well, perhaps it should be you, brother,
你对Hayley温柔献媚 款款深情
stealing my child away with every fawning moment
然后就可以偷走我的孩子
of tenderness you show to Hayley.
这跟Hayley没关系
This has nothing to do with Hayley.
跟她什么关系都有！
It has everything to do with her!
她从刚来时就崇拜你
She's adored you since she arrived,
现在我的孩子 我的亲生骨肉
and now my child, my blood,
长大后要叫你爸爸
will grow up to call you father.
你就是这么想的吗？
Is that what this is?
你又担心自己会被抛弃吗？
You are once again worried that you will be left behind?
这么些年你就没点儿长进吗？
Has history taught you nothing?
不是我们抛弃你 Nik
We don't abandon you, Nik.
是你疏远了我们
You drive us away.
真的吗？
Is that so?
我最近难道不是一直很配合你们吗？
What have I done lately other than cooperate?
我听从于你 哥哥
I bowed down to you, brother,
为了弥补我再次捅了你
to make up for daggering you,
为了我们夺回家园的宏伟计划
for the greater good of our plan to reclaim our home;
而看看你 妹妹
Looked the other way, sister,
你却又跟Marcel纠缠不清
while you repeat the same cycle with Marcel,
栽在这个你不该爱的男人身上
falling again for a man you shouldn't be with,
而他却统治着这个由我们建立起的帝国
while he controls the empire that we built
他占为己有
that he took.
对于过去犯下的过错 我无法否认
Now, I make no excuses for past sins,
但当那一刻 你们两个本可以
but in the one moment when you two could have
选择支持我 信任我
chosen to stand by me, to believe in me.
相信我对自己的骨肉没有什么不良企图
And believe my intentions for my own child were pure,
而你们却选择了敌对我
You chose to stand against me,
与我的敌人同流合污
to side with my enemies.
我想要夺回我们的家园
I wanted our home back.
现在我成功了
Now I have it.
所以我现在要去那儿生活
So I'm going to live there,
你们两个
and the two of you,
就呆在一起 慢慢腐烂在这里吧
you can stay here together and rot.
你得跟我走 小狼女
You're coming with me, little wolf.
我为什么要跟你走？
Why would I go anywhere with you?
因为你肚子里的孩子 Hayley
Because, Hayley, that child you carry
是我在这个世界上唯一关心的了
is the only thing on this earth that matters to me.
你可以以此跟我作对  但你斗不过我的
Now, you can fight me on this, but you will lose,
任何阻止你上车的人
as will anyone else who tries
也不会得逞
to stop you getting in this car.
我弄明白了 这个记号
I figured it out, the note.
我一直在想我遗失的时间
I was thinking about it-- my lost time,
还有我昏沉沉的大脑
my fog brain.
我觉得我一定是跟Sean一样疯了
I thought I must be going crazy like Sean,
但后来我想 是不是我的潜意识
but then I thought, "What if somewhere
在给我暗示呢？
in my subconscious, I was trying to send myself a message?"
《皮卡尤恩日报》1919
确实
I was.
我在1919年的《皮卡尤恩日报》里发现了这个
I found this in the "Picayune" newspaper archives from 1919.
看这张照片
Look at this photo.
那些人 我见过
Those men, I know them.
他俩我都认识
I know both of them.